[Slow, seductive double bass melody]
[Spooky by Dusty Springfield plays]
♪ In the cool of the evening
When everything is getting kind of groovy
♪ You call me up and ask me
♪ Would I like to go with you
And see a movie
♪ But first I say no
I've got some plans for tonight
♪ And then I stop
♪ And say alright
♪ Love is kind of crazy
With a spooky little boy like you
♪ You always keep me guessing
♪ I never seem to know
What you are thinking
♪ And if a girl looks at you
♪ It's for sure
Your little eye will be a winking
♪ I get confused
♪ 'Cause I don't know where I stand
♪ And then you smile
♪ And hold my hand
♪ Love is kind of crazy
With a spooky little boy like you
♪ Spooky
♪ If you decide someday to stop
This little game that you are playing
♪ I'm gonna tell you all the things
My heart's dying to be saying
♪ Just like a ghost you've been
A haunting my dreams
♪ So now I know
♪ You're not what you seem
♪ Love is kind of crazy
With a spooky little boy like you
♪ Spooky
♪ Oh, oh, spooky
♪ Alright, spooky ♪
[Music fades, resonates]
[Delicate chimes]
[Soft ambient music joins]
[Music fades]
[He groans]
[He mutters to himself]
So how does Daddy survive exactly?
I don't think there's any social security
'cause I don't really recall him
ever having a 'real' job.
Yeah, I...
I'm not completely sure.
You know,
he always seems to have projects.
[Woman] Uh-huh.
He's gonna look old, isn't he?
Well, yeah, I guess.
You said it's been two years?
Give or take, yeah.
I remember you
flew back here to see him.
[Woman] We met at a restaurant.
He said his place wasn't, uh, presentable.
[Man] Well, yeah. It probably wasn't.
[Woman] I still think about mom's funeral.
That wasn't good.
He was very upset though.
Hmm.
The last time he called me,
well, the last times he called me
you know, he puts on a little show.
The 'Dad' act, but...
you know in the end,
it's always about money.
Did you give him any?
[Woman] No.
Well, a few years ago I did.
Richard was furious
when he found out I'd sent it.
But after that, no way.
You?
Well, yeah. Sure, I've...
I helped him out here and there.
Man, Sheryl didn't like it either.
[Woman] It's probably
why she divorced you.
I'm sorry. I didn't--
I shouldn't have said that.
It's okay.
There were other reasons.
I'm sorry, Jeff.
You see this?
[Dreamy ambient music]
Man, those skater kids are everywhere.
They grow like weeds, right?
[Woman] My Louis is a skater.
[Music fades]
He's the anarchist of the family.
[Jeff chuckles]
How old is he now? Twelve?
Thirteen.
[He mutters to himself]
[Rapid footsteps]
[Soft clattering]
I did feel I needed to help him out
for those few, you know, emergencies.
What are you talking about?
The well, and the septic disaster.
You knew about that, right?
No.
Well, he really needed help, so...
And then the wall thing.
The wall thing?
[Jeff] Yeah.
This wall collapsed,
and part of his house apparently caved in.
Or almost did.
Come on, Emmy.
He called you about that, no?
No.
Huh. Wow.
Man, that was expensive.
He told me recently
he can barely pay for electricity.
Or the phone bill.
His landline?
Yeah, his landline.
Dad's place is just over
this next hill, I think.
Or maybe the next one.
Okay.
[Car indicator ticks]
[Emily] Nowheresville.
Should probably get this driveway graded.
[Emily] Okay.
[Birds call]
I brought a few things for him.
Of course you did.
That's not looking too good.
[Birds call in background]
- [Father] Hey!
- [Emily] Oh, hi, Daddy.
- [Jeff] Hi, Dad, it's us.
- Hey, Emily. Come on in, Jeff.
- [Father mutters to himself]
- Come on in.
Yeah.
- [Jeff] Excuse me.
[Father] Okay.
[Father mutters to himself]
Okay, well, you look fantastic.
And you don't look any older.
That's debatable, but thank you.
Hey, that's a really great color on you.
Oh, thanks.
And on you, too.
Oh, what a nice sweater, Jeff.
Oh, look at that.
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
I think it's a family thing.
[Jeff and Emily chuckle softly]
Yeah.
Alright, so here we go.
- [Emily] Sorry.
- Oh, sorry.
Well, it's good to see you, son.
You've always been my favourite son.
Well, your only son.
As far as we know.
There's that same
sense of humor, huh?
Come on inside.
Okay.
[Jeff] Oh.
Yeah.
Welcome.
Oh, I like this chair.
Oh, oh, yeah.
That, that's a special chair.
Friend of mine made that and, uh...
It's nice 'cause it swivels
and you look out the window.
[Father mutters to himself]
- [Emily] Oh, this is really nice, Daddy!
- [Father] Isn't it?
- [Emily] So peaceful.
- [Father] Yeah.
Uh...
[He chuckles] What is this?
These are just some things
I brought for you.
Oh, wow. Oh, gosh!
Wow, thanks.
I... um, looks like real,
real quality here.
[Father clears his throat, grumbles]
Well, have a seat, darling.
Make yourselves at home.
- Thanks, Dad.
- Thank you.
Hey, your furniture is kinda stylish.
I like it.
- Yeah, it's old.
- [Father chuckles]
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's still in pretty good shape.
[Father] Okay. Thanks.
Uh...
I want you guys to know
that I'm so glad you're here.
It really means a lot to me.
And it's so great to see you both.
And, and I know it's been a while.
Can I get you anything?
Some, how about some water or...
Oh, is it your, your well water?
Is the pump and all that fixed?
Yeah. All working now, you know.
All working thanks to you.
Thank you, son.
Let's get a little water going.
[Metal squeaks;
Water gushes]
What about ice?
I think I got ice around here.
Oh, no. Thanks though.
- I'd like some ice.
- [Father] Oh, good. Ice coming up.
I wish I had some lemon
or something to go with it.
Okay.
Here comes the water.
Oh, oh. Thanks, son.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Well...
Let's have a toast to, um...
Um...
To your wonderful mother.
To... to our wonderful mother.
- I'll drink to that. To mom.
- [Father] Yeah.
[Father swallows audibly, exhales]
Is it okay to toast with water though?
Oh, gosh. I... I think so.
It's the purest drink.
[He grumbles]
And your mother loved water.
And don't forget
she was a water sign, you know.
Aquarius is a water sign?
- Yeah. Aquarius is a water sign.
- [Father] Yeah.
Ah.
Not a water sign,
but it's a water carrier.
[Water drips in the background]
Do you hear that dripping?
What is that?
Oh, it's the...
It's the kitchen faucet.
You can't seem
to shut it off tight enough, and...
But it does go away after a while.
[Water continues dripping]
[Father sighs]
Wow. Wilhelm Reich,
'The Mass Psychology of Fascism'.
I didn't realize you read
this kind of thing, Daddy.
Uh... I had interests.
It's been a while.
[Emily] Noam Chomsky.
Oh!
Diogenes? Interesting.
Father of cynicism.
[She chuckles]
That's appropriate.
How are things back home, Em?
How are the kids?
Both are doing well.
Jennifer is a junior in high school.
She's very smart and confident, and...
Louis is in middle school.
He's in a bit of
an awkward phase, but...
he's finding himself.
[Father] And... what about Richard?
Fine. Solid as a rock.
- [Father] Alright.
- As always.
Uh, Jeff, how's Sheryl?
[She clears her throat]
Uh...
I mean, do you still
even stay in touch, or...
No, Dad, we don't.
Oh, well, that's tough, man.
I'm, I'm really sorry.
What about work?
Is work going well?
Yes. Yeah, thanks.
I got, I...
I got that promotion I told you about.
And I... and yeah.
Working away.
Okay, well, hey,
I'm really proud of you, son.
I mean, you've really done
well for yourself.
Well, thanks, Dad.
[Soft, pensive music]
Peaceful view, Dad.
With the pond, the trees,
and the horizon.
So quiet here.
[Father] Yeah.
It's a step away
from the so-called 'real world'.
[Music fades]
I made some tea.
[Jeff] Oh. Tea.
Yes. I found some
in the back of the cupboard.
[Jeff] Thanks, Em.
I could use some tea.
I didn't even know we had tea.
[Emily chuckles]
Oh! That's a nice watch, Daddy.
Is that a Rolex?
[Father] No, no.
Yeah, I mean it's a... it's a fugazi.
A Chinese replica.
I liked the style.
Huh. Well, looks real nice.
[He sighs] Yeah.
Hm.
What?
Um.
What do you say we... toast our tea to...
uh... family relations.
[She laughs] Oh, okay.
[Emily] Um, to family relations.
To family, then.
- To family.
- [Emily] To family.
[Emily chuckles softly]
[Father chuckles softly]
- Hmm.
- Hm. Good?
Excellent. Yeah.
[Bird calls in the distance]
Can you toast with tea though?
- Well.
- Really?
[Father chuckles softly]
- [Father sighs]
- [She slurps tea softly]
[He swallows, audibly]
[Soft, pensive music]
[Jeff] I just wanna show you
some things I got for you.
[Father] Oh. Wow.
These are a few packages of pasta.
- Very good ones.
- Oh, yeah.
[Jeff] Italian.
And some marinara sauce
with the cheese already in there.
Oh, it's so much easier for me.
- Thank you.
- And crackers, cookies.
- Yeah, oh, yeah, cookies.
- Jar of dill pickle spears.
Yeah, oh!
- Canned tuna,
- Oh, man.
...and then that French mustard you like.
- [Father] Oh, thanks for remembering.
- [Jeff] Good stuff.
[Father] Yeah, yeah.
I got some fruit.
Apples, a few oranges.
- That's the good stuff.
- Yes. Got some of this.
Heaven's Door!
Mezcal, too.
And some apple juice.
Okay. Thank you. Thank you.
There's some dried ramen noodles
in there too.
Oh, man. You got everything.
Thank you!
- Much appreciated, son.
- [Jeff] No problem.
Yeah. And thank you, too, Em.
Oh no, that's all from Jeff.
- [Father] Oh, well.
- [Emily] So kind of him.
[Father] Yeah. Yeah.
It's wild because you're planning
on going into town,
doing a grocery shop,
you know, and then your kids show up
on the front porch,
and I get this box
with all this great stuff in it,
and Bob's your uncle.
Um...
English expression.
"Bob's your uncle".
But Ted's our uncle.
[Father] Never mind.
[Father laughs]
Hey, Dad, do you want me
to take a look back
where the wall was rebuilt last fall?
No, no. It's... it's fine.
It's probably pretty muddy
and snowy back there.
I don't care about the mud.
I don't really want you
to deal with it right now.
I'm... trying to...
Trying to what?
I'm trying to... uh...
well, there's a busted pipe, and...
Ah, well, let me just take
a quick look then.
No, no, son!
No! I don't want
to deal with it right now.
I just want to be together
and have this time...
to spend together.
I just don't want to have to...
- worry about it right now.
- Okay, Dad.
Yeah.
Are you gonna be okay with heating fuel
for the rest of the winter?
Prices are outrageous.
Oh, yeah. I know they are.
But I've got
this beautiful wood stove here.
I chop my own wood.
I'm like a real country bumpkin here.
- [Emily chuckles, clears her throat]
- You know, I got the...
I...
I know what I'm doing around that.
It's good and therapeutic for me
'cause I...
there's nothing
that feels as good as chopping.
You know what I mean?
When I'm chopping, I'm on it,
chopping and focused and chopping.
I-I-I just, I don't know.
I chop!
And I chop! And I chop!
Whoa, okay, whoa!
Oh, god, I...
You're scaring me.
I... That, that was wrong.
I... I'm sorry.
Sorry, honey. I got carried away.
Sorry, sorry. I'm...
Yeah. Mm-hmm.
[He groans, softly]
Daddy, how's, um...
how's your health in general these days?
Everything okay?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm good.
I'm good, in general.
- [Soft, uneasy music]
- Any, any recent episodes?
- [Father] What do you mean?
- Uh...
Like... you know,
like at mom's funeral.
- [Music increases]
- [He sighs]
Yeah. That, that was some time ago.
But that, that was a particular... thing.
Particular thing, yeah.
Uhh, very emotional.
Yeah.
Yeah, for us all.
[Father] Yeah, well, you two...
handled it admirably.
[Music concludes]
May I ask if you still take anything?
Take anything?
Well,
I take my coffee in the morning.
Yeah.
I mean like any medication.
Well, no. No. No.
[He mumbles]
No, nothing like that. No. Really.
Nothing like that.
If, if that's what you're asking me,
I-I don't...
No, I don't, I don't take drugs.
I do have a drink now and then.
But, no. Nothing. No, no...
no heroin, no cocaine,
no fentanyl, no oxycontin.
No LSD,
no marijuana.
No uppers, no downers.
No goofballs, no... toad skins,
no... and you know,
no horse tranquilizers.
Okay. Daddy. I just...
[Jeff chuckles]
I'm just asking if you take
any medication like,
like prescriptions.
No.
You think I should?
No. I didn't say that.
I just, I just want you to feel good.
Yeah, um...
Okay. I-I-I do.
I feel good.
"Just like I knew that I would."
Well, can I get you anything else?
Any more water or tea,
or... maybe some of Jeff's bourbon?
Oh, thanks, Dad.
I'm... I'm driving.
But, uh... you know, it's getting late,
we should probably get going.
Yeah. Yeah.
[Father] Oh, gee, okay.
Well, I-I-I could make dinner.
I have the pasta.
I have the... spaghetti sauce
which has the cheese already in it.
I could-- Oh!
Or even you know...
You remember cookie chicken?
I remember cookie chicken.
- Oh, yeah.
- You think I can make cookie chicken?
Or ramen, or...
I act-- I wish we could.
- [Father, sighing] Oh.
- Hm.
But... maybe next time.
Yeah. Good.
- [Jeff] Yeah.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
I wish you could stay longer.
It's been really great seeing you.
You really gotta go?
- Yeah.
Well, gee, I...
Well, okay.
Okay.
- Love you, darlin'.
- I love you, Daddy.
[Father] Thanks for comin' to see me.
Okay. Love you.
Okay. I love you, too, son.
Thanks for coming.
- Great seeing you.
- Good seeing you.
- To tide you over.
- Oh! No.
No, no.
I really appreciate it, son.
Yeah.
- Okay.
[Jeff] Dad, your truck.
What?
Kinda looks like shit.
Does it even run?
[Father] Oh, yeah. The Chevy?
Oh, yeah. It's a little rough.
A little rough,
but she's an old workhorse.
[Jeff] Really?
Doesn't look like it.
Hey, nice ride, son.
Oh, yeah. It's a hybrid.
I lease it.
Hybrid.
[Jeff] Well, great to see you, Dad.
Great to see you, son.
Love you, darlin'.
- Bye, Daddy.
- [Father] Bye.
Love you.
Hey, thanks for coming out
and seeing your old Dad!
[Jeff] Yeah.
[Engine starts]
[Car horn beeps]
[He sighs]
Oh, this really is some quality stuff.
[He mumbles to himself]
Yep. Yep.
[He groans]
Well, that was strange.
I don't really know what to think.
[Jeff] I think he was happy to see us.
But as they say,
you can choose your friends,
and your lovers
but you can't choose your family.
I wasn't talking about you, Em.
It's okay.
I know what you meant.
He's always been a real character.
A little mysterious.
Yeah.
Did he act kinda crazy
even when we were little, though?
Yeah, but usually in sort of a fun way.
[He huffs]
But later on, he wasn't really
in my life all that much.
I... I kind of lost the connection.
[Jeff] I always wanted to look up to him.
I tried to, anyway.
Well, I'm glad we saw him.
Thanks for doing that.
Sure. I'm glad too.
Sort of.
Did you see that Rolex, though?
That was real.
- Nah.
- Yep.
Really?
[Footsteps approach]
[He mutters to himself]
Hey, Charlotte. Yeah. What's up?
Oh, yeah? That's interesting.
Hey, listen.
You...
you know,
I came into some unexpected cash,
and I wondered if you wanted to meet me
down at Shades for dinner and drinks?
The whole bit.
Yeah. My treat, of course.
Yeah, um...
Oh, good.
It'd be good to see you, too.
Um.
Listen, you get there before I do,
tell Tommy we want the usual booth.
You know the routine.
Yeah. Good.
Alright. Twenty minutes.
I'll see you soon, baby.
Bye.
[He inhales]
[He exhales]
[Soft, pensive music]
Okay.
[He inhales, exhales loudly]
A little on the...
[Engine starts]
[Music fades]
[Delicate chimes]
[Soft ambient music joins]
[Music concludes, fades]
[Birds cheep;
Dog barks in distance]
[Indistinct voice on phone]
Yeah, well, I'm very happy
to see them on the one hand, but...
I just have to keep them
from stirring things up, you know?
Yeah.
Yeah, I still see them.
Now once a year,
together, for afternoon tea.
Our yearly ritual.
Yeah, it really was
an excellent suggestion on your part.
Mm-hmm.
And we do speak on the phone.
Every few weeks at least.
Well, Timothea calls
more frequently than Lilith.
Yeah. She... she seems
more in need of me,
even though she's the older one,
you know.
At times,
she seems totally lost in the world.
But somehow, I...
I worry more about Lilith.
Hm.
[Clock chimes]
Oh, dear. Our time is almost up,
and they'll be arriving shortly.
Thank you so much
for doing a phone session.
You are so very helpful, like a navigator.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll see you next week, then?
Thank you. Next Tuesday.
Bye now. Bye.
[Grandfather clock ticks softly]
[Brakes squeak]
[Seagulls shriek]
[Loud clunk;
Engine hum cuts out]
[Engine stops]
Oh... darn it.
That's the ID number.
Yeah. Correct.
Uh... Murtagh Road.
Wha-- 45 to an hour?
Oh, gosh.
Okay, um.
[Disconnected tone]
Hello?
[Baby gurgles in background]
Hello, Mummy?
[Mother, on phone] Hello, dear.
Is everything alright?
[Woman] No, actually.
My wretched car has broken down.
I'm stuck by the side of the road.
Oh, no. I'm so sorry.
I'm going to be late now.
- Don't worry.
- [Woman] I'm so sorry.
Lilith's not here either,
and she's often late anyway.
[Woman] Ha, yes.
You don't need me
to come get you, do you?
No. I've called
the Automobile Association already.
Ah, Automobile Association to the rescue.
[Woman] Yes, indeed.
Okay. Take care, darling.
Thanks for calling.
- See you soon.
- [Woman] Thanks, Mummy.
Do you really only
see your ma once a year?
And not even on a holiday?
Yeah. No, we don't really
do holidays together.
But you have tea.
How very fucking traditional of you.
It is kinda weird you and your sister
moved to Dublin to be near your ma,
and then only see her, like, once a year.
Yeah. I guess the set-up is kinda strange.
Seems like you two grew up
like butterflies floating
around each other in different directions.
Do you ever miss living elsewhere?
Yeah.
Yeah, I miss Brussels.
I loved it there.
Living all on my own.
Yeah, you know you do sometimes
kinda sound, sort of Belgian.
Yeah? Well, you always fucking sound
- Irish!
- Irish.
Yeah. I'm well aware of that.
- I met your sister once.
- Yeah?
Timothea, right?
- Tim.
- She's nice.
- Yeah.
- How is she?
I don't know.
[Loud rattling]
[Dreamy ambient music]
[Music fades]
So when we get close,
I just wanna jump
in back seat before we arrive, okay?
And, why?
I thought I told you.
'Cause if we pull up
and my mum sees us,
I can tell her I took an Uber.
So, I'm your Uber driver? Really?
Well, you've got the hat.
Fuck off!
Sorry.
I'll tell her my Lexus is in the dealers.
- Your Lexus?
- Yeah! My new Lexus!
[Woman 2] So, as your Uber driver,
am I supposed to pick you up?
Doesn't your sister live
way far in the other direction?
Yeah, she lives in Nowheresville.
No, I'll ask my mum to call me an Uber
and then it'll be on her account.
So somewhere around here,
you can pull over,
and I'll get in the back.
Okay.
My chauffeur.
[Lilith] Fuck off.
[Engine sputters]
[Engine starts]
Yes. I'd like to cancel a service call
I made a little while ago.
Murtagh Road.
Yes. 7-7-2-3-3-5-3.
Thank you.
[She groans]
[Doorbell rings]
Got you.
- Hi, Mum.
- Hello, Lilith.
I like your hair.
Oh, thank you!
I like your outfit, too.
Yeah. Oh, you're ridiculous.
[Lilith chuckles]
Look at my bag.
Designer bag.
Yeah. It was on sale.
Really?
Place looks amazing. Love it.
Well, thank you.
Actually it's exactly
the same as last year.
I'll take your-- oh!
- Just here.
- Okay.
Shall we sit and chat?
- Until Tim arrives.
- Yeah. Here?
- [Mother] Yeah.
- [Lilith] Yeah.
She called to say she had car trouble.
- Oh!
- And then she called to say she was fine.
- So...
- Okay.
So, I don't know.
Yeah.
And you? I saw you came
with a car service.
Yeah. Yeah, well, I have a Lexus.
A beautiful new one.
Almost new.
But the dealer has it.
It's being detailed.
It's a service they provide.
- Is that right?
- Yeah.
Well, that's a nice perk.
Yeah, so I came in an Uber.
So pretty.
I was going to bring you some.
But then the plan became awkward
with the Uber and everything.
Well, it's sweet of you
to think of me in any case.
So, how is everything?
Are you still with
the gloriously handsome Robert?
You never met him!
[Mother] No, but you texted me photos.
Without his shirt on, I might add.
[Lilith] Yeah...
it's a while ago.
Well, he wants to marry me,
but I don't know, you know.
[Mother] Well, that's exciting.
- You didn't tell me.
- No.
Well, what are your thoughts?
[Lilith] I have mixed thoughts, really.
He is rich, and handsome.
And says he adores me too.
And seems to.
[Mother] Oh, I should hope so.
Yeah.
[Mother] Well, how do you feel?
I don't know, Mum.
I'm not sure if I wanna be,
you know, tied to a man.
[Mother] Hmm, well...
You have to be sure, I guess.
If you want to make it work.
[Lilith] Yeah.
Yeah.
[Grandfather clock ticks softly]
[Vehicle approaches]
Your sister is here.
[Lilith] Oh, wonderful.
Hello, Mummy.
Timothea. How lovely to see you.
[Mother chuckles softly]
[Timothea chuckles;
Door closes]
Look who's here!
Oh.
Hello, Tim.
Hello, Lilith.
[Timothea chuckles softly]
You look fantastic!
Oh, my, I don't know
about that, but you do.
- Oh, it's so nice to see you.
- Yeah.
Let me take these beautiful flowers.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
I'll take your coat.
Okay.
[Timothea clears her throat]
[Lilith chuckles softly]
Well, we seem to be
accidentally color coordinated.
How embarrassing.
Oh. Yes, it is, isn't it?
- I love it.
- Do you really?
Yeah. Red.
- I'll put these lovely flowers in a vase.
- Yes.
So, how is everything?
Lil, it's... all good?
- Yeah.
- I hope?
Yeah. Fantastic.
Yeah. Good.
I almost hate to say it,
but my life's kinda been like a dream.
Oh, great.
- Yeah.
- Good. That, that's great to hear.
And you?
Me? Oh, well, oh...
You know. Ups and downs.
But everything's, everything's, it's good.
- I think.
- Yeah?
Yeah. I love your hair.
Thank you.
- So cute.
- [Lilith] Yours too.
[Timothea] Yes. So, um...
- Mum looks good.
- Yeah.
- Doesn't she?
- Yeah. She looks great.
She doesn't look old to you, does she?
Ah, no.
I... I think she looks great.
- Yeah, she does.
- Yes.
Yeah. Amazing.
Reckless Moonlight.
Do you know about this one?
Yes. I saw it on the bestseller list.
Put it back.
Lilith. You know she doesn't like talking
about her books with us.
I know, I know.
The Boundaries of Love.
- And Lilacs In The Snow.
- [She whispers] Lilith, stop it, please!
[Timothea gasps softly]
An Unfaithful Tomorrow.
Girls.
Shall we go to the table?
Hey.
Wait for Mummy.
No. No, this won't do.
Oh!
That's much better.
But your flowers were much more--
Loud.
[Mother] Well, let's say prominent.
No, no. These are lovely.
It's perfect. Much better.
[Mother clears her throat]
[Timothea clears her throat]
[Lilith clears her throat]
So, shall I be mother?
You might as well start sometime.
[Mother chuckles]
[Timothea] Oh. Thank you.
Mummy?
Thank you.
It's wonderful to see you both.
Thank you for coming.
Thank you, Mummy.
Thanks, Mum.
Mm.
[Timothea] Lil!
Fuck, that is so good!
That looks delicious.
Where, where do you get that from again?
Oh, there's my very favourite
little shop
in town that always
has all the things I like.
You know, Walkers' shortbread fingers,
MacKay's marmalade, PG Tips tea.
And sometimes they just have
these delicious little cakes.
So, whenever I crave one
of my favourite treats,
I just pop down there,
and your uncle's name is Robert!
[All laugh lightly]
Mmm, love 'em!
Oh, it's heavenly.
[She slurps loudly]
[Lilith] Mm.
[Timothea] Mm.
Lil!
Sorry, I really...
I just, I have this big sale online
of some vintage clothes,
and I have to close it.
Lil, not at table.
Mmm. This tea is so good, Mummy.
There. All done.
It is.
I think the water makes
all the difference.
Do you use bottled or filtered water?
I try to drink only pure bottled water
from Iceland.
From Iceland?
Is that right?
Well, for tea this water
has been boiled,
but the water here is filtered.
That's good to know.
- I still drink tap water, so...
- [Lilith gasps]
[Lilith] No, you shouldn't, Tim.
I've heard people getting
their tap water tested,
and they found horrible things in it.
You know, like cocaine, Covid,
E. Coli, amoebas, antibiotics,
fentanyl, all kinds of shit.
Lilith, that's terrible.
Where do you hear such things?
Some... podcast or something.
Oh, Lil.
So, Tim,
what does your tap water taste like?
Well, I don't know.
It just tastes like water.
I mean, does water even have a taste?
Well, of course it does.
It tastes like... water.
[Timothea] Yeah.
[Softly] Hm.
So, girls...
please give me some news.
How's everything going?
Oh, um...
You know...
Each year I check my Chinese horoscope,
- and I'm a Sheep, you know?
- And a Capricorn.
Yes. And every year
it says the same thing. It says,
"Another year with numerous
minor obstacles
"but the sheep will remain good-natured,
and you know, plod along."
Does it really say "plod along"?
Yes, well, something like that.
[Mother] But your good nature
is a wonderful gift, though.
Thank you--
My Chinese sign is...
- A Dragon.
- A Dragon. Yes, we know that.
And usually, it says the dragon
will have another fantastic year,
with adventure and romance.
And is this true?
Hm, yeah.
No complaints really.
[Mother] Hmm.
[Birds chirp outside]
[Timothea sighs]
Well, I do have some good news
I'd like to share.
Oh?
[Timothea] I've been promoted.
Tim!
I'm now on the executive board
of the Heritage Council.
Fantastic, Tim!
Yes! You know the one that decides
which old buildings
in Dublin will be protected.
[Mother] Well, that's wonderful news!
Have you started yet?
Well... the first full meeting's
next week, but yes.
I am very excited.
- [Lilith] Cool.
- Yes.
[Mother] I'm very proud of you, Tim.
And all your work.
And I always have been.
Well, thank you, Mummy.
I really do appreciate that.
Oh!
I have some good news too!
Do you?
[Mother] Yes.
So, I have a number of new clients.
I call disciples.
Part of my community.
And they're all very popular influencers.
Well... that sounds like a good idea.
[Timothea] Influencers?
Can you explain that to me?
[Lilith] Oh boy, not now.
I'm sorry.
I didn't want to interrupt your news, Tim.
I can tell you both about it another time.
But we are interested.
[She sighs, softly]
[Teacups clink]
May I be excused?
- I just...
- Yes, certainly, dear.
I need to go to the loo.
[Mother] Tell me a joke.
[Lilith] Mm, so, in the universe,
three planets are floating,
and they're having a grand time,
having tea, PG tips.
"Oh, how're you?",
"I'm good. How're you?"
And then there's a third planet
that comes along, and looks like shit.
Coughing.
And they say, "What is it with you?
Why are you looking so shit?"
And then he says, "Oh, you know,
"it's just that I've caught this thing.
"It's called humanity."
And then they laugh,
and they say, "Oh, that's okay.
"That one goes away."
[Mother laughs]
- That is good!
- [Lilith] Yeah.
[She breathes shakily]
Hm.
[Mother and Lilith laugh downstairs]
[Mother and Lilith talk indistinctly]
Like my new watch?
Oh, yes. That's nice.
Oh, my!
Is that a Rolex?
Yes.
Oh! Very nice.
You can't tell it's fake, can you?
I... I bought it on Moore Street
from some guys.
Don't you love it?
Hmm.
Oh, it's later than I thought.
Oh, it's not. Is it really?
But it seems you only just got here.
Yes. We've only just got here.
Well, time flies when you're having fun.
[Lilith clears her throat]
[Soft, uneasy music]
[Music increases]
[Music fades]
Some little things for each of you.
With some of the cakes you like.
[Timothea] Oh.
I hope your little car
will be running perfectly.
Oh, yes. I think it's fine. Fine.
And I assume you called an Uber.
Um...
Hey, Lil, would you like me
to give you a lift home?
Oh, no, no. Thanks, sis.
Not sure your car would make it.
No, that's sweet of you,
but it's an hour in the other direction.
And anyway, I was going to make
some important calls on the way back.
So, um... Mum,
I feel really bad to even ask,
but I had some trouble
with my Uber account on the way here,
so, I was wondering--
But, dear, they brought you here,
so I'm sure it's fine.
Yeah, no. It's not going to work
on the way back.
Yeah. I can't explain really.
But... if I could use your account.
You know, I'm kinda stressed out about it.
Of course.
Of course, darling.
I'll call you one.
- [She sighs]
- Thanks a million, Mum.
I'll pay you back.
There. You put in your destination.
Okay.
Seven minutes.
I'll wait with you
til the Uber comes then.
- Alright, then.
- Hm.
[Clock chimes]
Three minutes.
[Seagulls shriek]
[Engine approaches]
Goodbye, darling.
- Bye bye, Mummy.
- Bye.
[Bird cheeps]
[Soft, pensive music]
[Engine starts]
[Music fades]
[Soft ambient music]
[Dreamy ambient music]
[Music fades]
[Man, in French] Careful,
they're stronger than last time.
- Okay. A plus.
- A plus.
[In English] Thanks for waiting.
Appreciate it.
[Sister] Seat belt.
So, did you meet your weed guy there?
[Brother] No, I get shrooms from him.
[Sister] You still smoke
a lot of weed these days?
Weed or hash rarely.
But shrooms, yes.
I micro-dose.
Little amounts each day.
I know what micro-dosing is.
[Train screeches]
I could sorta tell you were doing it.
- [Brother] Really?
- Yeah.
- [Brother] You could feel it?
- Mm-hmm.
Did you start recently?
Like maybe a month ago,
while I was in New York?
Exactly. Like four weeks ago.
So, you can even sense
the effects of a micro-dose?
Sorta. Twin factor.
Twin factor.
Plus that psilocybin is just
some crazy shit, bro.
[Brother] Saved my life in a way.
You know, it resets everything.
Brings everything back to zero.
Where each moment, is each moment.
- Yeah. I could use some of that.
- [Sirens wail nearby]
- [Brother] You smoke any weed these days?
- No, no.
I try to stay as clear
as possible these days.
Life is...
tripped out enough for me.
[Brother] Hm.
[Sister] So, this is gonna be kinda weird.
Going back to the apartment.
It'll be okay.
I... I guess it is kinda weird
with all their stuff cleared out.
Thanks again for doing it all.
It's all good.
It's Mom and Dad.
- Wanna get a coffee for a second?
- [Sister] Yeah.
Where should I go?
I don't know, uh...
Take a left up there.
[Car indicator ticks]
[Birds cheep;
People chat indistinctly]
[In French] Thank you.
[In English] Good idea to get a coffee.
It's comforting.
[Brother] Right?
Hey. Where are you?
I'm just in Nowheresville.
Nowhere special.
Yeah, I've been there.
What are you doing?
Just looking at this water.
And?
I was just... thinking about
this cool Indigenous girl I met.
She kept referring to water
as... medicine.
[Sister] Hmm.
I don't know. It just keeps
coming back to me.
Damn.
This whole world is so fragile.
Yeah, no shit.
Aren't you glad we have...
We had... such unconventional parents?
Yeah, I mean, who wants to be a square
and live a conventional life?
True.
I guess being twins is already
kind of unconventional.
Being your twin sure is.
I mean, I'm also sure
there's a bunch of twins out there
that are total fucking squares.
True.
This is a weird question,
[She inhales]
but do you think the plane
still would've crashed
if Mom was the one who was flying it?
Knowing her...
probably not.
They said it was some
weird weather-related thing.
Who knows.
Didn't we talk about this already?
Those small planes
are so fucking dangerous.
Yeah, well so are motorcycles.
Yeah, at least on a bike
I'm not way up in the fucking sky.
No. You're not. Not literally.
[He sighs]
I assume you still have your bike?
Yeah. My '84 Kawi 650.
[Sister] That beat-up old black thing?
- That's my baby.
- [Sister laughs softly]
[He sighs]
It's like you said, though.
The world is really fragile, I think.
Anything can happen. It's all so...
random.
So, how's your love life, Boobie?
You beating 'em back with a shovel?
Oh, shut up.
[Brother] I really do think you should
move back here for a while though.
Plus, you can keep their car.
I love that thing.
Classic Volvo 1800.
I don't want their car.
I'm not sure what I'm gonna do.
Well...
to quote the great Groucho Marx,
"Whatever it is, I'm against it."
[Sister laughs]
Yeah, no shit.
[Brother slurps loudly]
Can you toast with coffee, though?
It doesn't matter.
[Brother sniffs]
Ahh!
- [Both burp]
- Brutal.
Always.
Should we get the fuck outta here?
[Sister] Yeah, let's go.
[Brother, in French] Thank you.
Thank you.
[Waiter] Goodbye.
[Train horn blares]
[Brother, in English] Hey.
Do you feel any side effects
from that weird virus
now that it's been a few months?
No. Not really.
It was nice that you called
before I said anything though.
Yeah, it was weird.
Just for a moment,
I thought I was getting it too.
So... then I called you.
- Twin factor.
Everything good now though?
Virally speaking, yeah.
Oh shit.
What the fuck?
[Brother sighs]
[Sister] Aren't we, like, a block away?
It doesn't even look familiar.
Yeah. It all changes so fast.
It's all so fucking...
Impermanent.
Yeah.
We're almost there though.
[Car engine shuts off]
[Siren wails in distance]
Mom's old trick.
Yeah. Hope it still works.
[He exhales]
- [He clears his throat]
- [Electronic beeps]
Hey.
[In French] Hello.
[Footsteps, echoing]
I used to love this staircase
when we were kids.
[Brother] Same.
[Door lock clicks]
[Traffic hum increases]
You're dead.
[Soft, pensive music]
You alright?
Yeah.
Just thinking about Dad's cooking.
Yeah. It was good.
So good.
[Music continues;
Bell tolls]
Mom and Dad's room.
[Music fades]
[He inhales, exhales deeply]
[Soft, pensive music resumes]
[Music increases, undulates]
[Music concludes]
[Creaky footsteps]
Water?
- Medicine.
- Yep.
[She swallows loudly]
Really?
Listen, man,
I wouldn't wanna mix up our molecules.
Yeah, fuck you.
And your damn molecules.
Saved some shit I wanna show you.
Billy. You did all this
since we last spoke?
Yeah.
Organized it all.
Packed it all up.
Sent it to storage.
Packed.
And... about two truckloads.
Well, two vans anyways.
[Sister] Hmm.
That's amazing.
Thank you.
I am so impressed you organized it all.
Especially impressive for such a fuck up.
Thanks.
It wasn't actually that bad though.
Drove each load over,
packed into the storage unit, and...
- Bob's your uncle!
I love you.
Check this out.
- [Sister gasps]
- This one first.
[Sister] Wow.
I love this.
I wanna keep this.
Take it.
I scanned all these.
[Sister] We didn't come out looking
that much alike, did we?
- [Brother] Really?
- [Sister] I don't think so.
It's a good thing, too.
Otherwise, I'd be
too beautiful to deal with.
[He chuckles]
That's true.
Look at this one.
[Sister] Damn, they were hot!
I never saw this one.
Look at Dad! A total fox.
What's that?
A marriage license?
Didn't Mommy say
that she would never, ever get married?
They didn't.
Did a little research, and...
it's all fake.
What?
I think they must have needed it
for something involving the authorities.
[Sister] It sure looks real.
[Brother] It's not.
She fabricated the whole thing.
Well, maybe them
not getting officially married
is what kept them together
in the first place.
[Brother] Maybe. Yeah.
I'd like to think that maybe, you know,
their deep love
had something to do with it.
[Sister] You think?
[Brother] Check these out.
[Sister] Our birth certificates.
Are these fake, too?
[Brother] No. I think they're real.
But didn't Mommy say that
she lost our actual birth certificates?
Yeah, I know.
Man, she was problematic.
Tell me about it.
Wow.
So this makes us...
actual, real-life New Yorkers.
- This is proof.
- [Brother] Yeah.
We're native New Yorkers.
And our passports are legit.
Wow.
That's so fucking cool.
Oh... my God!
[Sister chuckles softly]
Miss Falci's class.
- This is you.
- [Brother] That's me.
[Sister] We argued about the colors
of the hats that we were gonna use.
[Sister, laughing] I remember.
[Brother] We do look a lot alike though.
[Sister] We do.
I think you got the eyes right.
[Brother] The beady eyes.
[Sister] And who thinks
of a double-seat bike when you're like,
how old were you, like 6 or 5?
We were so innovative.
Look at this.
This is crazy.
[Sister] Dad is from California?
Look how young he is.
Wow!
And Mom is from Ohio.
Yep. Look. South Carolina.
Jersey. Texas.
[Sister] What?
[Sister laughs]
And I got to keep
Dad's beat-to-shit Rolex too.
[Sister] Wasn't this Granddad's?
[Brother] That's what Dad said, yeah.
[Sister] I'm surprised
he wasn't wearing it.
[Brother] Yeah, me too.
But... nope.
[Sister] It suits you.
Dependable, cool.
Little rough around the edges.
Just like you.
Wait. I got one more thing.
You're really, really gonna love this.
[Sister] Mom.
Man, she's such a movie star.
But wait.
[She gasps] Oh, my God!
Okay.
Wait.
[She clears her throat]
You can totally rock those.
- You look sick. You look really sick.
- Yeah?
- You think so?
- Yeah.
You look tight.
Not as good as her.
- Ahh, debatable.
- [She laughs]
I love you so much.
Thanks for being my brother.
I got you, man.
Love you, too, Boobie.
We're gonna be okay.
Duh.
I got a little box of other
stuff for you at my place.
Just objects.
Little things I thought, you know,
had their mojo in them.
I kept a box too, but...
you can have whatever you want.
Did they keep a lot of our old stuff?
Oh, yeah.
Toys, photos, drawings.
They kept like every drawing
we ever made.
They even kept the principal's letter
from that one time we got suspended.
- Wow.
- You'll see.
It's not like
I threw anything away, its all...
carefully packed into storage.
Good luck finding anything though.
It's... mad full.
What are we gonna do with it all?
I don't know.
Do we have to know right now?
No. Can't really deal with it.
[Sirens wail in distance]
[Keys jingle;
Door opens]
[Brother, in French] Oh, Madame Gautier,
you startled us.
What are you two doing here?
[Brother] Just here for a last visit.
But this is no longer your apartment.
Skye just got back.
We wanted to say goodbye
one last time.
You know your parents, bless their souls,
still owed three month's rent.
As I told you, Billy,
the agency could've seized all they had.
Yes.
[In English] She was nice enough
to prevent that,
and let me move everything out.
[Madame Gautier] Yes, I did.
I kept my word with you, Billy.
I hope I won't regret it.
Okay.
[In French] Give me back the keys
when you leave.
I will. Thank you.
[Sister] Thank you, Madame Gautier.
I'm very happy to see you again.
It's nice to see you, my little Skye.
[Sister] Ciao.
[Door closes]
[Sister] Do you ever think about
where they died?
[Brother] Does it matter?
Where you die?
[Sister] I don't know.
Like, do we even know why
they were flying a plane in the Azores?
[Brother] Do we even know why they were
ever doing anything anywhere?
I mean...
[Bells toll in the distance]
[Metal rattles]
[Sister gasps]
[Sister] Oh my God.
It's Mom's favourite song.
Oh, yeah.
Do it.
[Spooky by Dusty Springfield plays]
♪ In the cool of the evening
♪ When everything
Is gettin' kind of groovy
♪ You call me up and ask me
♪ Would I like to go
With you and see a movie
♪ First I say no
♪ I've got some plans
For tonight and then I stop
♪ And say alright
♪ Love is kind of crazy
♪ With a spooky little boy like you
♪ You always keep me guessing
♪ I never seem to know
What you are thinking
♪ And if a girl looks at you
♪ It's for sure
Your little eye will be a winking
♪ I get confused
'Cause I never know where I stand
♪ And then you smile
♪ And hold my hand
♪ Love is kind of crazy
With a spooky little boy like you
♪ Spooky
♪ Spooky... ♪
- [Music fades]
- [Car indicator ticks]
Eighteen.
[Metal clanks, squeals]
Damn, Billy.
You really cleaned them out.
[Brother] Yeah.
And this unit goes back way deep too.
It never really seemed
like they had that much shit.
But... they really squirreled
a lot of stuff away.
[She sighs]
[Sister] Shit really adds up, don't it?
[Brother] Half of this stuff is still
boxed up from our grandparents.
[Brother exhales]
What are we gonna do with it all?
I don't know.
[Brother] Do we have
to know right now, though?
[Sister] No.
Can't really deal with it.
[Metal clanks, rattles]
[Footsteps recede]
[These Days by Nico plays]
♪ I've been out walking
♪ I don't do too much talking these days
♪ These days
♪ These days I seem to think a lot
About the things that I forgot to do
♪ And all the times
I had the chance to
♪ I stop my rambling
♪ I don't do too much gambling these days
♪ These days
♪ These days I seem to think about
How all the changes came about my way
♪ And I wonder if I'd see another highway
♪ If I had a lover
♪ I don't think I'd risk another
These days
♪ These days
♪ And if I seem to be afraid
To live the life that I have made in song
♪ It's just that
I've been losing so long ♪
[Slow electric guitar joins]
♪ I'd stop my dreaming
♪ I won't do too much scheming these days
♪ These days
♪ These days I sit on cornerstones
And count the time in quarter tones to ten
♪ Please don't confront me
With my failures ♪
[Slow electric guitar resumes]
♪ I've not forgotten them ♪
[Music fades, stops]
[Dreamy ambient music]
[Music continues]
[Music concludes]
[Ruminative ambient music]
[Music fades]